<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss" xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#" >

<channel>
	<title>Webbeneur</title>
	<atom:link href="/oof/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/oof</link>
	<description>How to Make Money Online</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 00:10:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<!--Theme by MyThemeShop.com-->

<image>
	<url>/oof/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/cropped-webbeneur-70x70.png</url>
	<title>Webbeneur</title>
	<link>/oof</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>4 Rules for New Entrepreneurs</title>
		<link>/oof/4-rules-new-entrepreneurs-practical-tips-starting-right/</link>
		<comments>/oof/4-rules-new-entrepreneurs-practical-tips-starting-right/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 23:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Michael Webb]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/oof/?p=613</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>It’s a great time to be an entrepreneur—in the last decade, technology has leveled the playing field and propelled an entrepreneurial revolution. As an entrepreneur, you now have more access to information that enables you to make more intelligent choices more quickly. You have an advantage over big businesses in that you’re lighter, more flexible, and faster on your feet. You can target new markets more quickly, and you can turn on a dime. But being a successful entrepreneur requires that you look at the big picture and follow a plan through from beginning to end. Rieva Lesonsky, editor-in-chief of </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oof/4-rules-new-entrepreneurs-practical-tips-starting-right/">4 Rules for New Entrepreneurs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/oof">Webbeneur</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It’s a great time to be an entrepreneur—in the last decade, technology has leveled the playing field and propelled an entrepreneurial revolution. As an entrepreneur, you now have more access to information that enables you to make more intelligent choices more quickly. You have an advantage over big businesses in that you’re lighter, more flexible, and faster on your feet. You can target new markets more quickly, and you can turn on a dime.</p>
<p>But being a successful entrepreneur requires that you look at the big picture and follow a plan through from beginning to end. Rieva Lesonsky, editor-in-chief of <a href="https://www.entrepreneur.com/">Entrepreneur Magazine</a> gives some practical guidelines that can help you when beginning your own enterprise:</p>
<hr />
<h2>4 Rules for New Entrepreneurs</h2>
<p><strong>1. Don’t Quit Your Day Job.</strong><br />
Consider starting your business part-time, especially if it’s online, while you’re working and have a steady income. It usually takes six months to a year to get a business going and you don’t want your ability to make your house payment to hinge upon your company being an overnight success. Start with what you can manage, financially and time-wise, and scale up as your business grows.</p>
<p><strong>2. Find Your Niche.</strong><br />
The days of general stores are over. Particularly online, consumers are looking for stores that specialize. You have to find a need—something a specific group of people want, but can’t get at the big chain stores—and fill it. Advises Lesonsky, “You can’t compete with the big guys, so you have to find where the big guys aren’t and go into your niches.”</p>
<p><strong>3. Have an Online Presence.</strong><br />
Even if you’re not planning to start an online retail business, consider that the internet can still play a valuable role in your company. Having an online presence eliminates the limitations of physical location and broadens your customer base by, literally, millions. It’s also a great tool for promoting yourself and letting people, even in your own area, know that you’re there, and what you’re doing.</p>
<p><strong>4. Refuse to Quit.</strong><br />
Successful entrepreneurship requires creativity, energy, and a drive to keep going when you fail. Few people realize that before Bill Gates created the extremely successful Microsoft 3.0, he created a Microsoft 1.0 and 2.0, both of which flopped—but he kept at it. And that determination and refusal to give up is what will separate successful entrepreneurs from unsuccessful ones. Says Lesonsky, “Arm yourself with optimism to get beyond the ‘No’ or the trouble. There’s nothing wrong in failure—just don’t repeat the same mistake!”</p>
<hr />
<h2><strong>Watch this video for 5 more great tips</strong></h2>
<div class="flex-video flex-video-youtube"><iframe width="770" height="433" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fQyn34NZ_24?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<hr />
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://www.amazon.com/Art-Start-2-0-Time-Tested-Battle-Hardened/dp/1591847842/ref=pd_sbs_14_t_0?_encoding=UTF8&amp;psc=1&amp;refRID=T7XFJ537SAXV3ZVWTRGX"><strong><span id="productTitle" class="a-size-large">The Art of the Start by Guy Kawasaki</span></strong></a><br />
Whether you&#8217;re an aspiring entrepreneur, small-business owner, or not-for-profit leader, this is a MUST-READ for anyone starting anything! Written by a marketing specialist, author, and Silicon Valley venture capitalist.</p>
<div class="button-center"><a href="https://www.amazon.com/Art-Start-2-0-Time-Tested-Battle-Hardened/dp/1591847842/ref=pd_sbs_14_t_0?_encoding=UTF8&#038;psc=1&#038;refRID=T7XFJ537SAXV3ZVWTRGX" target="_self" class="buttons btn_green center"><span class="left"><i class="fa fa-shopping-cart"></i> Buy The Art of the Start</span></a></div>
<hr />
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oof/4-rules-new-entrepreneurs-practical-tips-starting-right/">4 Rules for New Entrepreneurs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/oof">Webbeneur</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/oof/4-rules-new-entrepreneurs-practical-tips-starting-right/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Risks of Entrepreneurship</title>
		<link>/oof/the-risks-of-entrepreneurship/</link>
		<comments>/oof/the-risks-of-entrepreneurship/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 20:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Michael Webb]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/oof/?p=556</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The &#8220;spark&#8221; for many entrepreneurs is seeing an opportunity that doesn’t yet exist. Ted Turner, for example, launched CNN because he perceived that people wanted more television news than they were being offered. It took a lot of patience on Turner’s part to realize the vision, but he had read the market in a way that few &#8220;experts&#8221; did at the time. In realizing the promise of CNN, Turner demonstrated another facet of the entrepreneurial spirit, persistence. There are a lot of bright ideas that never reach fruition; taking a &#8220;raw&#8221; idea and converting it into a successful business model </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oof/the-risks-of-entrepreneurship/">The Risks of Entrepreneurship</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/oof">Webbeneur</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The &#8220;spark&#8221; for many entrepreneurs is seeing an opportunity that doesn’t yet exist. Ted Turner, for example, launched CNN because he perceived that people wanted more television news than they were being offered. It took a lot of patience on Turner’s part to realize the vision, but he had read the market in a way that few &#8220;experts&#8221; did at the time.</p>
<p>In realizing the promise of CNN, Turner demonstrated another facet of the entrepreneurial spirit, persistence. There are a lot of bright ideas that never reach fruition; taking a &#8220;raw&#8221; idea and converting it into a successful business model is very hard work.</p>
<p>And that work never stops. No matter how innovative your idea, the competition is always just behind you. With anything less than constant creative effort on your part, they may not stay behind you.</p>
<p>Are you still with me? Here is where I reveal why everyone isn’t an entrepreneur:</p>
<p>No opportunity is a sure thing, even though the path to riches has been described as, simply &#8220;&#8230;you make some stuff, sell it for more than it cost you&#8230; that&#8217;s all there is except for a few million details.&#8221; The devil is in those details, and if one is not prepared to accept the possibility of failure, one should not attempt a business start-up.</p>
<p>It is not indicative of a negative perspective to say that an analysis of the possible reasons for failure enhances our chances of success. Can you separate failure of an idea from personal failure? As scary as it is to consider, many of the great entrepreneurial success stories started with a failure or two.</p>
<hr />
<h1>Steve Jobs on Failure</h1>
<div class="flex-video flex-video-youtube"><iframe width="770" height="578" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zkTf0LmDqKI?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<h2><a href="http://amzn.to/2hxMAeT">&#8220;Most people never ask and that&#8217;s what separates the people who do things from the people who just dream about them. You&#8217;ve got to act, and you&#8217;ve got to be willing to fail. You&#8217;ve got to be willing to crash and burn. If you&#8217;re afraid of failing you won&#8217;t get very far.&#8221;</a> &#8211;<strong>Steve Jobs</strong></h2>
<hr />
<p>Some types of failure can indicate that we may not be entrepreneurial material. Foremost is reaching one&#8217;s level of incompetence; if I am a great programmer, will I be a great software company president? Attitudinal problems can also be fatal, such as excessive focus on financial rewards, without the willingness to put in the work and attention required. Addressing these possibilities requires an objectivity about ourselves that not everyone can manage.</p>
<p>Other types of failure can be recovered from if you &#8220;learned your lesson.&#8221; A common explanation for these is that &#8220;it seemed like a good idea at the time.&#8221; Or, we may have sought too big a &#8220;kill;&#8221; we could have looked past the flaws in a business concept because it was a business we wanted to be in. The venture could have been the victim of a muddled business concept, a weak business plan, or (more often) the absence of a plan.</p>
<hr />
<h2><strong>Top 3 Reasons Small Businesses Fail:</strong></h2>
<p><strong>1.</strong> <strong>inadequate financing often due to overly optimistic sales projections</strong></p>
<p><strong>2.</strong> <strong>management shortcomings</strong><br />
&#8212;inadequate financial controls, lax customer credit, inexperience, and neglect</p>
<p><strong>3.</strong> <strong>misreading the market</strong><br />
&#8212;indicated by failure to reach the &#8220;critical mass&#8221; required in sales volume and profitability<br />
&#8212;usually due to competitive disadvantages or market weakness</p>
<hr />
<p>In a Wall Street Journal article titled &#8220;Why My Business Failed,&#8221; Ken Elias cautions that &#8220;even if the concept is right, it won&#8217;t fly if the strategy is wrong.&#8221; Still, on being asked whether he would start another business today, he answers: &#8220;Absolutely. The experience is fabulous, exciting and the possibility of success is always there.&#8221;</p>
<hr />
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://amzn.to/2hxMAeT"><strong><span id="productTitle" class="a-size-large">Steve Jobs by Walter Isaacson</span></strong></a><br />
Failure is a stepping stone towards success. One of my favorite innovators is Steve Jobs &amp; his biography shows the importance of taking risks &amp; learning from failures. It&#8217;s a MUST-READ book for entrepreneurs.</p>
<div class="button-center"><a href="http://amzn.to/2hxMAeT" target="_self" class="buttons btn_green center"><span class="left"><i class="fa fa-shopping-cart"></i> Buy Steve Jobs Biography</span></a></div>
<hr />
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oof/the-risks-of-entrepreneurship/">The Risks of Entrepreneurship</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/oof">Webbeneur</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/oof/the-risks-of-entrepreneurship/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Does It Take to Be an Entrepreneur?</title>
		<link>/oof/what-does-it-take-to-be-an-entrepreneur/</link>
		<comments>/oof/what-does-it-take-to-be-an-entrepreneur/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 18:47:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Michael Webb]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/oof/?p=544</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the years countless institutes and individuals have asked the million dollar question. What makes an entrepreneur an entrepreneur? What traits or characteristics are inherent to a successful entrepreneur and is one born with those traits? There’s great news! Successful entrepreneurs are born every day! Some people believe an entrepreneur is born while others believe an entrepreneur can be taught. Some believe an entrepreneur is like an artist &#8211; either you have it or do you don’t. Some see entrepreneurs as leaders that are focused, disciplined, competitive, and charismatic, while others see them as huge risk takers. And all of </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oof/what-does-it-take-to-be-an-entrepreneur/">What Does It Take to Be an Entrepreneur?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/oof">Webbeneur</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over the years countless institutes and individuals have asked the million dollar question. What makes an entrepreneur an entrepreneur? What traits or characteristics are inherent to a successful entrepreneur and is one born with those traits? There’s great news! Successful entrepreneurs are born every day!</p>
<p>Some people believe an entrepreneur is born while others believe an entrepreneur can be taught. Some believe an entrepreneur is like an artist &#8211; either you have it or do you don’t. Some see entrepreneurs as leaders that are <strong>focused</strong>, <strong>disciplined</strong>, <strong>competitive</strong>, and <strong>charismatic</strong>, while others see them as huge <strong>risk</strong> <strong>takers</strong>. And all of these analogies are right to some degree.</p>
<p>It’s true all successful entrepreneurs share a few qualities and skills that allow them to be successful. These inherent qualities can be taught; but they often seem to be an inherent driving force that sends individuals down the path of being in business or formally training for a career in business.</p>
<p>Entrepreneurs <strong>see the world differently</strong>. They have the ability to see the world as a system. They have the ability to see something in its entirety and as an integrated unit, and they seem to possess the ability to <strong>see opportunity</strong> within the global picture. They are what is called a system thinker.</p>
<hr />
<h1>Become an Entrepreneur &#8211; Motivational Video</h1>
<div class="flex-video flex-video-youtube"><iframe width="770" height="433" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hf0oGW3Pj4Y?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<hr />
<p>There are other characteristics they possess. Entrepreneurs possess an overpowering need to <strong>achieve</strong> and tend to be very <strong>competitive</strong> against themselves. They are continuously trying to outthink themselves and others and they are constantly looking for the edge. This is a process that occurs as naturally as breathing and is a driving force behind most entrepreneurs.</p>
<p>They have the <strong>determination</strong> and <strong>dedication</strong> to follow through with commitments and they always appear <strong>confident</strong> and in control. You’ll notice they also possess a positive atmosphere. They are of the mindset “I can,” and “I will.” They are not afraid of failure because failure is not in their vocabulary nor is it an option.</p>
<p>They are objective but have the ability to weigh risks realistically within the big picture. They have an uncanny ability to anticipate developments which gives them the edge on many competitive situations. Entrepreneurs seem to feel right from their gut, call it <strong>instinct</strong>. They are a <strong>resourceful</strong> group that possess excellent problem solving skills and are able to diligently work through obstacles as they occur.</p>
<p>Entrepreneurs are <strong>excellent communicators</strong> and recognize how important clear and concise communication is to their success. They also possess a sound working <strong>knowledge</strong> of the business they are involved in.</p>
<h2><a href="http://amzn.to/2i3MdpA">“A person&#8217;s success in life can usually be measured by the number of uncomfortable conversations he or she is willing to have.”</a> –Tim Ferriss</h2>
<p>When it comes to successful entrepreneurs it’s a question of what came first, the chicken or the egg. Is it inherent qualities that we are born with that lead us to be entrepreneurs or is it when we choose to become an entrepreneur that we develop the skills and qualities of success? That’s a question we shall leave to the great debaters to resolve.</p>
<p>What is for certain is that successful entrepreneurs are born every day and that <strong>you too can be a successful entrepreneur by developing the skills of success.</strong></p>
<hr />
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://amzn.to/2i3MdpA"><strong><span id="productTitle" class="a-size-large">The 4-Hour Workweek: Escape 9-5, Live Anywhere, and Join the New Rich</span></strong></a><br />
Want to learn more about the tools of success, entrepreneurship, and how to escape your 9-5? If you&#8217;re serious about becoming your own boss and living the good life, you HAVE TO READ this bestseller!</p>
<div class="button-center"><a href="http://amzn.to/2i3MdpA" target="_self" class="buttons btn_green center"><span class="left"><i class="fa fa-shopping-cart"></i> Buy The 4-Hour Workweek</span></a></div>
<hr />
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oof/what-does-it-take-to-be-an-entrepreneur/">What Does It Take to Be an Entrepreneur?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/oof">Webbeneur</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/oof/what-does-it-take-to-be-an-entrepreneur/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>32 Motivational Mark Cuban Quotes</title>
		<link>/oof/32-motivational-mark-cuban-quotes/</link>
		<comments>/oof/32-motivational-mark-cuban-quotes/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 03:59:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Michael Webb]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Quotes]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/oof/?p=457</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Mark Cuban is the owner of the NBA&#8217;s Dallas Mavericks, Landmark Theatres, and Magnolia Pictures, and is the chairman of the HDTV cable network AXS TV. He is an entrepreneur, investor, author, and TV personality, appearing on the hit TV series Shark Tank, alongside Kevin O&#8217;Leary, Barbara Corcoran, Daymond John, Robert Herjavec, and Lori Greiner. Billionaire Mark Cuban has a lot of powerful advice for entrepreneurs on his blog, in his book, and within these short inspirational quotes. Check them out, and enjoy! 32 Mark Cuban Quotes 1. “Don’t start a company unless it’s an obsession and something you love. If you </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oof/32-motivational-mark-cuban-quotes/">32 Motivational Mark Cuban Quotes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/oof">Webbeneur</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mark Cuban is the owner of the NBA&#8217;s Dallas Mavericks, Landmark Theatres, and Magnolia Pictures, and is the chairman of the HDTV cable network AXS TV.</p>
<p>He is an entrepreneur, investor, author, and TV personality, appearing on the hit TV series Shark Tank, alongside Kevin O&#8217;Leary, Barbara Corcoran, Daymond John, Robert Herjavec, and Lori Greiner.</p>
<p>Billionaire Mark Cuban has a lot of powerful advice for entrepreneurs on <a href="http://blogmaverick.com/">his blog</a>, in <a href="http://amzn.to/2hM87ON">his book</a>, and within these short inspirational quotes. <strong>Check them out, and enjoy!</strong></p>
<hr />
<h1>32 Mark Cuban Quotes</h1>
<p><strong>1.</strong> “Don’t start a company unless it’s an obsession and something you love. If you have an exit strategy, it’s not an obsession.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>2.</strong> “I love to compete. To me, business is the ultimate sport. It’s always on. There is always someone trying to beat me.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>3.</strong> “Creating opportunities means looking where others are not.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>4.</strong> “Wherever I see people doing something the way it’s always been done, the way it’s ‘supposed’ to be done, following the same old trends, well, that’s just a big red flag to me to go look somewhere else.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>5.</strong> “Small businesses don’t fail for lack of capital. They fail for lack of brains, they fail for lack of effort.” <strong>–</strong><strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>6.</strong> “The key is having great players. But there are a lot of teams that have All-Stars and haven’t been able to put it together.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<h2><a href="http://amzn.to/2hM87ON">“If you’re going to compete with me or one of my businesses, you’d better recognize that I’m working 24 hours a day to kick your ass.”</a> –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></h2>
<p><strong>8.</strong> “Doesn’t matter if the glass is half-empty or half-full. All that matters is that you are the one pouring the water.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>9.</strong> “What I’ve learned is that if you really want to be successful at something, you’ll find that you put the time in. You won’t just ask somebody if it’s a good idea, you’ll go figure out if it’s a good idea.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>10.</strong> “Social media is just a platform. Twitter is a very simple and immediate broadcast platform. Facebook is a very personal, when it comes to friends and when it comes to fan pages, a little bit less but still somewhat personal way to communicate.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>11.</strong> “Make sure you are the boss. I don’t think I would encourage executives that work for me to blog. There can be only 1 public vision for an organization.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>12.</strong> “In my opinion, right now there’s way too much hype on the technologies and not enough attention to the real businesses behind them.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<h2><a href="http://amzn.to/2hM87ON">“Business is a sport 24/7/365.”</a> –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></h2>
<p><strong>14.</strong> “The only thing any entrepreneur, salesperson or anyone in any position can control is their effort.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>15.</strong> “When you’ve got 10,000 people trying to do the same thing, why would you want to be number 10,001?” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>16.</strong> “What I’ve learned in these 11 years is you just got to stay focused and believe in yourself and trust your own ability and judgment.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>17.</strong> “Money is a scoreboard where you can rank how you’re doing against other people.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<h2><a href="http://amzn.to/2hM87ON">&#8220;Once you have found out what you love to do, there is only one goal: to be the best in the world at it.”</a> – <strong>Mark Cuban</strong></h2>
<p><strong>19.</strong> “Work like somebody is trying to take it all away from you.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>20.</strong> “For every one of my businesses, what would I have to do to kick my own ass? What ever business you have, there is always someone trying to put you out of business. It’s better for you to figure how they’re going to do it, than they do it.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>21.</strong> “There are always going to be things we love to do. That we dream about doing. That we really, really want to do with our lives. Those passions aren’t worth a nickel.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>22.</strong> “Being rich is a good thing. Not just in the obvious sense of benefiting you and your family, but in the broader sense. Profits are not a zero sum game. The more you make, the more of a financial impact you can have.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>23.</strong> “When you turn your team upside down and try to figure out what the culture of the team is, you take the greatest risk a team can take.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>24.</strong> “Because if you’re prepared and you know what it takes, it’s not a risk. You just have to figure out how to get there. There is always a way to get there.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>25.</strong> “Find something you love to do. If you don’t make money at it, at least you love going to work.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<h2><a href="http://amzn.to/2hM87ON">“It doesn’t matter how many times you have failed, you only have to be right once.”</a> –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></h2>
<p><strong>27.</strong> “Sweat equity is the most valuable equity there is. Know your business and industry better than anyone else in the world. Love what you do or don’t do it.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>28.</strong> “I worked hard and smarter than most people in the businesses I have been in. It’s not in the dreaming, it’s in the doing.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>29.</strong> “I’m a believer that you accomplish much, much more with direct relationships than by using an intermediary. And that cash you keep in the bank can be the difference between staying alive as a small business, or not.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>30.</strong> “It’s not about money or connections — it’s the willingness to outwork and out-learn everyone… And if it fails, you learn from what happened and do a better job next time. We are acting in the best interests of shareholders.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>31.</strong> “What I do know, at least what I think I have learned from my experiences in business, is that when there is a rush for everyone to do the same thing, it becomes more difficult to do. Not easier. Harder.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<p><strong>32.</strong> “You’ve gotta be differentiated and unique. You’ve gotta know what your core competency is and be great at it.” –<strong>Mark Cuban</strong></p>
<hr />
<h1>19 Important Lessons From Mark Cuban</h1>
<div class="flex-video flex-video-youtube"><iframe width="770" height="433" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/aZHCgKHAwjQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<hr />
<p>Thanks for checking out this awesome list of Mark Cuban quotes!</p>
<p>Don’t forget to check out our other awesome quote collections. Get motivation and wisdom from entrepreneurs like Bill Gates, Richard Branson, Warren Buffet, and many others.</p>
<p><strong>What’s your favorite Mark Cuban quote? Leave a comment below.</strong></p>
<hr />
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://amzn.to/2hM87ON"><strong><span id="productTitle" class="a-size-large">How to Win at the Sport of Business: If I Can Do It, You Can Do It</span></strong></a><br />
Did you know Mark Cuban has published a whole book filled with even more business knowledge? If you liked these quotes, you&#8217;ll LOVE Mark&#8217;s book. In fact, many of these quotes came from the book!</p>
<div class="button-center"><a href="http://amzn.to/2hM87ON" target="_self" class="buttons btn_green center"><span class="left"><i class="fa fa-shopping-cart"></i> Buy Mark Cuban&#8217;s Book</span></a></div>
<hr />
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oof/32-motivational-mark-cuban-quotes/">32 Motivational Mark Cuban Quotes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/oof">Webbeneur</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/oof/32-motivational-mark-cuban-quotes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
